jonomus.net 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

> ### Personal Information

We only collect personally identifiable information that you choose to provide on our Website during registration process at Jonomus.net.  
We also collect email addresses for communication purposes only.  
Jonomus does not trade, sell, deal your Personal Information with anyone.

> ### Non-Personal Information

Jonomus.net also collects certain other information from you on your visit to our Website such information about your  device type, browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, operating system,your internet service provider and your IP Address

> ### Cookies

Our Website Jonomus.net use cookies to enhance User experience.  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies. If they do so, it may affect overall experience with us.

> ### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on jonomus.net. Google’s DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Jonomus.net and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  
Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon  
Flipkart  
Snapdeal

> ###  **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure of your personal information, stored on our Site.

> ###  **Children’s privacy**

Jonomus.net requires that the visitor must be at least 15 years old to use our site. If you are below 15 years of age, you are strictly prohibited from registering on our Website.

> ###  **Changes to this privacy policy**

Jonomus.net has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [admin@jonomus.net](mailto:admin@jonomus.net)

(Visited 305 times, 1 visits today)
